

0424891952 toddy9229@outlook.com Melbourne, VIC 3134 GitHub: @todd0554

EXPERIENCE

Warehouse Manager Launceston, Tasmania P & M Asian Town

Mar 2019 to Dec 2021

- · Taking the responsibility of loading and unloading work
- Drafting purchase plan every week
- Training new staff

Casual Warehouse Staff Melbourne, Victoria Maltra Foods

Feb 2022 to Jul 2022

- · Picking and packing
- Manipulate mechanical equipment to finish work

SUMMARY

I'm a web development student with background in Maritime Design. I have three years warehouse working experience. The experience of learning my master degree brings me strong mathematics background and dependent self-learning ability which makes me be able to acquire unfamiliar knowledge quickly. I'm looking for an internship of front-end.

SKILLS

- Be able to use Github to develop with other developers
- Familiar with basic knowledge of HTML, CSS and Javascript
- Be able to use React, node.js, MangoDB and Express to develop web app
- Be able to use ROR and Postgresql to develop web apps
- Be able to use different deploying tools including Heroku, Netlify and Railway
- Basic Bootstrap 5 skills
- · Good teamwork and collaboration
- Self-Motivated and Dependent learning

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Diploma of Web Development Feb 2022 to Nov 2022 Code Academy Melbourne Vic Australia

Master of Maritime Design Jul 2016 to Jul 2018 University of Tasmania Launceston Tas Australia

Bachelor of Mechanical Engineering And Automation Jul 2011 to Jul 2015 Jiangxi University of Science And Technology Ganzhou Jiangxi China

CODING PROJECTS

BandFleaMarket – A music instrument two side marketplace based on ROR

• Github repo: click HERE

My portfolio – A simple introduction website of myself

Github repo: click HERE

CodeMusic – A terminal app based on ruby

• Github repo: click HERE

Dingo-Drum – A Hackathon team work app

• Github repo: click HERE